We will continue our longevity wellness at home.
We can use Figma.com to get some inspiration and parse it to the cursor.
So what I'm going to do, first I'll just open the cursor and our extension.
And I'll show you one of the pre-views, um, extension that I have used.
So in the past, I was creating the history trends extension.
This is the horse, it's like a placeholder, so no worries.
So if I press it, it will analyze my browsing history, see the visits, see visit URLs,
businesses and all of the things.
So now open a project, I will use the longevity.
So this is the longevity and obviously if I go back and upload longevity,
the extension here because I made it previously.
So if I go to longevity, I will open it.
Fortunately it has the same, same icon, so we'll just open it.
If you're on the right, we see reminders and favorites.
So if I go back to longevity extension, what I can do, I can go to Figma files
and now I can go to cursor.
I want you to make it more similar to this design
and implement communication goals to us achievements.
And we can make it as agent, so I will just open an agent.
And then when I have everything here, it will just try to make it.
I will add my previous extension to the file.
So if I have here, what I'm going to do is open longevity app.
So this is the longevity and I will copy my history trends extension,
because I will not use it.
I will use my history extension from analytics as just a module
that will try to look if this website is actually good for longevity.
If we are spending a lot of time for learning and as well for other things,
so we to just make it based on our entries and views and to time spend.
So this is the longevity to just compare it here.
And now if I go back to cursor, as you can see, history trends extension.
So now important, because the agent is still working, how we use this
and now we'll just make reference to it.
We don't need to always add it actually in our remote anyway.
I want to use this extension and combine with this design.
I will copy the figma.
So go back to figma.
And implement as a longevity module that will allow us to check our
browse history and adjust for longevity for both and give us some insights.
So it will be a bigger task and after that obviously we can even try to use
some of like AI, API, like DeepSick, it will help us to get more of the information around.
It will help us to get more of the information, but for us I will just try to make it
more simple and then on the agent, there is a possibility
to make our website of longevity and the new tap that I want to have it as the dashboard
that will not override and you tap because I'm using another extension.
So the dashboard should function like the one you have in this extension.
And now we just go to history trends.
I will accept it and now we'll be able to get, as you can see, we run three edges with huge
tasks. It might take some time because it will just be writing a code combining history trends
and again new model. So you'll post the video and return whenever you think it's ready.
So we're in three important comments and after that we'll just remove history extension
and test it out to see if it actually works.
I have a longevity extension. I will operate up with serial minders, drink water,
intermittent fasting, morning supplements, even the braving,
suicides, and return them, see if it's actually pop-ups every hour.
And now when I open a full dashboard, we see everything here.
So I'll add a new feature for reminders. Let me quickly change the time interval,
but to this cheap default settings. So I can test it out in a few seconds, give everything works.
And I will add a new agent, history, analytics is not working and I want to have a dashboard
of our own history and statistics with nice charts
and some summary based on our activity in terms of longevity.
I will run this to task and then I will come back to it.
And we got it more than six minutes and more than 24 hundred lines.
We have like API visualization, we've charged JavaScript, new dashboard features,
longevity health score, have metrics, improve user experience, and we have like some trends.
All right, so I'm going to test it out. I'm going to refresh it in a managed extension.
That's some error, so I'll fix them. But if I type it now, I see longevity extension,
I see references, I see the exercise, and this is the article to nature.
This is reminders every two hours. This actually doesn't work as I wanted,
so I'll just add an additional what we have history analytics, so it's not still not working.
I'll probably have to add some fix and what I'm going to do, I will just go to extension
and reminders. I'll just bring screen and what I'm going to do, open new agent,
I want to be able to add quickly timers for those tasks before values are okay,
but I want to change it. And now open new agent and the new agent, what I'm going to do,
I will go again to my history analytics step. And I will say that actually is empty, so
my history analytics step is empty. Maybe there is some error.
So now we just plan, we see restoration, the whole timer values.
If you were to remove the leftover comments,
this one will probably check all of it right, if it's like a list to check because
there's a lot of stuff to uncheck it. All right, this one is finished, and one is still in progress,
along with the history because the tab is not working. I cannot test it out because it's
actually implementing new things, so now we'll just add some changes to along with the history
JavaScript file. All right, it's finished, now I can reload, so we'll go back to my browser,
I'll refresh it, and manage extension tab. And now when I open it up, reminders,
and as you can see, now if I press it, I'm allowed to change it. It's not very easily,
and I have a thing that I want to make it like a more visible for end users,
so what I'm going to do, I will go to un-spot-ton, but make it more visible because
it looks like a text, and many users might not know that is a bigger one.
All right, and I will just make the last change for that. It will quickly, probably,
change the layout of that layout. It will update the CSS to make the frequency look more
like a clickable button. All right, we see if we can see now it's a button on plain
days, the background, it depends on how it looks like it looks like it looks tickable. And now we'll go, again,
change that extension, refresh it, and now when I open it up, yeah, now it looks like perfect,
because we can set up for ourselves.